const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What does the cartilage of the 3rd pharyngeal arch develop into?","answers":[{"option":"Greater horn of hyoid bone","bool":true},{"option":"Patella","bool":false},{"option":"Styloid process","bool":false},{"option":"Lesser horn of hyoid bone","bool":false},{"option":"Outer ear","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"A 63-year-old man fails to maintain balance during linear motion. Which of the following sensory organs is responsible for detecting linear acceleration?","answers":[{"option":"Saccules","bool":false},{"option":"Organ of corti","bool":false},{"option":"Maculae","bool":true},{"option":"Cristae","bool":false},{"option":"Cochlear duct","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is the most common location for a thyroglossal duct cyst?","answers":[{"option":"Superior mediastinum","bool":false},{"option":"Anterior to hyoid bone","bool":false},{"option":"At the base of tongue","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior to hyoid bone","bool":true},{"option":"Superior to hyoid bone","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"When the eye is medially rotated, what muscle is the prime depressor of the eyeball?","answers":[{"option":"Superior oblique","bool":true},{"option":"Medial rectus","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior oblique","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral rectus","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior rectus","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What nerve is the closest to the styloid process within the carotid sheath?","answers":[{"option":"Hypoglossal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus nerve","bool":true}]},{"id":5,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following fibers connect the Edinger-Westphal nucleus to short ciliary nerves?","answers":[{"option":"Postsynaptic sympathetic fibers","bool":false},{"option":"Presynaptic sympathetic fibers","bool":false},{"option":"Postsynaptic parasympathetic fibers","bool":false},{"option":"Presynaptic parasympathetic fibers","bool":true},{"option":"Somatic efferent fibers","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is true regarding the sternocleidomastoid muscle?","answers":[{"option":"When one side acts alone, the head moves downward","bool":false},{"option":"Forms floor of posterior triangle of neck","bool":false},{"option":"Covers cervical plexus posteriorly","bool":true},{"option":"Forms floor of the anterior triangle of the neck","bool":false},{"option":"It is innervated only by the accessory nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is true regarding nerves of the cervical plexus?","answers":[{"option":"Suboccipital nerve is purely a sensory nerve","bool":false},{"option":"The C4 anterior rami forms ansa cervicalis","bool":false},{"option":"The lesser occipital nerve supplies the anterior part of the ear","bool":false},{"option":"The C2 posterior rami forms greats occipital nerve","bool":false},{"option":"The C3 anterior rami contributes to the inferior root of the ansa cervicalis","bool":true}]},{"id":8,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is true regarding the temporomandibular joint?","answers":[{"option":"Masseteric nerve lies posterior to the joint","bool":false},{"option":"Anterior fibers of the temporalis muscle help in retraction","bool":false},{"option":"Protrusion occurs at the lower compartment of joint","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral movements take place in the vertical axis","bool":true},{"option":"The lateral pterygoid muscle retracts the mandible","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following structures does not pass through the foramen ovale?","answers":[{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Middle meningeal artery","bool":true},{"option":"Mandibular division of trigeminal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Lesser petrosal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory meningeal artery","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is the normal visual acuity?","answers":[{"option":"12/6","bool":false},{"option":"20/6","bool":false},{"option":"6/6","bool":true},{"option":"6/5","bool":false},{"option":"30/20","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"In the equation V=d/D used for visual acuity, what does 'd' stand for?","answers":[{"option":"Distance between the subject's two eyes","bool":false},{"option":"Distance between the subject and the doctor","bool":false},{"option":"Distance between the doctor and the Snellen's chart","bool":false},{"option":"Distance between the subject and Snellen's chart","bool":true},{"option":"Distance between the subject and the subject's romantic interest","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is the normal distance required between the subject and Snellen's chart to read it?","answers":[{"option":"12 meters","bool":false},{"option":"3 meters","bool":false},{"option":"6 meters","bool":true},{"option":"1 meter","bool":false},{"option":"9 meters","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What area(s) can we place the tuning fork on to perform the Weber's test?","answers":[{"option":"Middle of the scalp only","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Under the nose only","bool":false},{"option":"The middle of the forehead only","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What distance is required between the ear and the tuning fork to check air conduction in the Rinne test?","answers":[{"option":"3-5cm","bool":false},{"option":"5-6cm","bool":false},{"option":"4-5cm","bool":false},{"option":"9-10cm","bool":false},{"option":"1-2cm","bool":true}]},{"id":15,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is the normal range of intelligence quotient (IQ)?","answers":[{"option":"50-70","bool":false},{"option":"70-90","bool":false},{"option":"130-150","bool":false},{"option":"180-200","bool":false},{"option":"90-110","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What does distichiasis mean?","answers":[{"option":"Misdirected eyelashes","bool":false},{"option":"Outward protrusion of eyelid","bool":false},{"option":"Excessive sweating","bool":false},{"option":"Downward drooping of upper eyelid","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory row of eyelashes","bool":true}]},{"id":17,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is a fixation point used for?","answers":[{"option":"All of these","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"To immobilise the eye","bool":false},{"option":"To examine the pupil","bool":false},{"option":"To restrict eyeball movement","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Conductive deafness is caused by what?","answers":[{"option":"Defect in neural pathway","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Loss of eight cranial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Impaired sound transmission through the auditory canal","bool":true},{"option":"Defect in vestibule","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What structure is devoid of rods and cones?","answers":[{"option":"Neural layer","bool":false},{"option":"Optic disc","bool":true},{"option":"Fovea centralis","bool":false},{"option":"Macula lutea","bool":false},{"option":"Retina","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What embryological structure is the major source of the eyeball?","answers":[{"option":"Lens placode","bool":false},{"option":"Optic cup","bool":true},{"option":"Otic placode","bool":false},{"option":"Neural crest cells","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The primary palate is derived from which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Otic placode","bool":false},{"option":"Hypobranchial eminence","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary prominences","bool":false},{"option":"Two palatine shelves","bool":false},{"option":"Intermaxillary segment","bool":true}]},{"id":22,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following cells mainly causes lateral inhibition?","answers":[{"option":"Horizontal cells","bool":true},{"option":"Rods","bool":false},{"option":"Amacrine cells","bool":false},{"option":"Bipolar cells","bool":false},{"option":"Ganglionic cells","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What substance combines with scotopsin to form rhodopsin?","answers":[{"option":"All-trans retinol","bool":false},{"option":"11-cis retinol","bool":false},{"option":"All-trans retinal","bool":false},{"option":"13-cis retinol","bool":false},{"option":"11-cis retinal","bool":true}]},{"id":24,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which cell may cause excitation or inhibition in the retina?","answers":[{"option":"Ganglionic cells","bool":false},{"option":"Bipolar cells","bool":true},{"option":"Cones","bool":false},{"option":"Horizontal cells","bool":false},{"option":"Rods","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What area of the retina contains no rods?","answers":[{"option":"Outer nuclear layer","bool":false},{"option":"Macula","bool":false},{"option":"Granular layer","bool":false},{"option":"Fovea centralis","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What bony area has an H-shaped suture adjoining four skull bones?","answers":[{"option":"Lambda","bool":false},{"option":"Pterion","bool":true},{"option":"Asterion","bool":false},{"option":"Nasion","bool":false},{"option":"Glabella","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"A 35-year old woman presented to the clinic with a gradually growing nodule on her face. On physical examination, a 3cm nodular, non-tender, mobile mass is palpable on the left side of the face anterior to the area and just superior to the mandible. The biopsy of the nodule reveals ductal epithelial and myoepithelial cells along with cartilage in a myxoid stroma. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Acinic cell tumor","bool":false},{"option":"Burkitt lymphoma","bool":false},{"option":"Pleomorphic adenoma","bool":true},{"option":"Mucoepidermoid carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Squamous cell carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The hearing receptors are found on what membrane?","answers":[{"option":"Tectorial membrane","bool":false},{"option":"Basilar membrane","bool":true},{"option":"Tentorial membrane","bool":false},{"option":"Spiral membrane","bool":false},{"option":"Vestibular membrane","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The endolymph is found in what compartment?","answers":[{"option":"Scala tympani","bool":false},{"option":"Scala media","bool":true},{"option":"Middle ear cavity","bool":false},{"option":"Ductus reunions","bool":false},{"option":"Scala vestibuli","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is true about the second pharyngeal arch?","answers":[{"option":"Gives rise to the malleus and incus","bool":false},{"option":"Contributes to the epithelium of the dorsum of tongue","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Gives rise to muscles of facial expression","bool":true},{"option":"Forms the greater horn of the hyoid bone","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is not an error of refraction?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Myopia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypermetropia","bool":false},{"option":"Presbyopia","bool":false},{"option":"Emmetropia","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What statement is incorrect regarding the human eye?","answers":[{"option":"Photopic vision is the main function of cones","bool":false},{"option":"Contains fovea centralis fully packed with cones","bool":false},{"option":"Responds only to light of wavelength 600-750nm","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Scotopic vision is the main function of rods","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What structure does not act as a refractory medium for the eye?","answers":[{"option":"Vitreous humour","bool":false},{"option":"Aqueous humour","bool":false},{"option":"Cornea","bool":false},{"option":"Retina","bool":false},{"option":"Pupil","bool":true}]},{"id":34,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What statement is false regarding the sense of taste?","answers":[{"option":"Is lost in aguesia","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Is maximum for salty sensation","bool":true},{"option":"Is a chemical sense","bool":false},{"option":"Is called gustation","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What statement is false regarding photopic vision?","answers":[{"option":"It is mediated by cones","bool":false},{"option":"It does not use rhodopsin","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"It helps you see in the dark","bool":true},{"option":"It produces an image of fine resolution","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"A 35-year old female presented with dizziness for one day. She has a sense of rotation of the surrounding, most marked when lying on the left side. The Dix Hallipke maneuver is performed, with the patient asked to sit at the edge of the bed, moving her head 45 degrees on the left side, and then making her lie down with her head 30 degrees downwards. What will you observe to declare the test positive for benign positional vertigo?","answers":[{"option":"Gaze palsy","bool":false},{"option":"Nystagmus","bool":true},{"option":"Ptosis","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Hearing loss","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What can cause xeropthalmia?","answers":[{"option":"Conjunctival inflammation","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased keratinization of skin","bool":false},{"option":"Keratinization of cornea","bool":true},{"option":"Pleomorphic adenoma","bool":false},{"option":"Corneal infection","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What area of the retina is most concerned with the acuity of vision?","answers":[{"option":"Blind spot","bool":false},{"option":"Fovea centralis","bool":true},{"option":"Conjunctiva","bool":false},{"option":"Macula","bool":false},{"option":"Periphery of retina","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Night blindness is associated with abnormality in what cells?","answers":[{"option":"Ganglion cells","bool":false},{"option":"Bipolar cells","bool":false},{"option":"Amacrine cells","bool":false},{"option":"Rods","bool":true},{"option":"Cones","bool":false},{"option":"Horizontal cells","bool":false}]},{"id":40,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following angle is widest in the direction in the visual field?","answers":[{"option":"Upwards","bool":false},{"option":"Downwards","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Temporal","bool":true},{"option":"Nasal","bool":false}]},{"id":41,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following are photoreceptors of the retina of the eye?","answers":[{"option":"Melanocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Rods","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Rods and cones","bool":true},{"option":"Cones","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Taste buds are present in the following papillae except:","answers":[{"option":"Fungiform","bool":false},{"option":"Fulliform","bool":false},{"option":"Foliate","bool":false},{"option":"Circumvalate","bool":false},{"option":"Filliform","bool":true}]},{"id":43,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"A 57-year-old man with human immunodeficiency virus (HIV) presents to the outpatient department with complaints of dysphagia. On examination, a whitish pseudomembranous was seen on the oropharynx and tongue. This pseudomembrane was scraped off when it tried to scrape it. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Oral candidiasis","bool":true},{"option":"Erythroplakia","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes labialis","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Leukoplakia","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The light entering the eye passes to which layer of the retina first?","answers":[{"option":"Pigmented layer","bool":false},{"option":"Ganglionic cell layer","bool":true},{"option":"Bipolar layer","bool":false},{"option":"Inner plexiform layer","bool":false},{"option":"Receptor cell layer","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What structure forms the lateral wall of the infratemporal fossa?","answers":[{"option":"Posterior surface of the maxilla","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral pterygoid plate","bool":false},{"option":"External acoustic meatus","bool":false},{"option":"Zygomatic arch","bool":false},{"option":"Ramus of mandible","bool":true}]},{"id":46,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following structures is not crossed by light when entering the eye?","answers":[{"option":"Aqueous humor","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Cornea","bool":false},{"option":"Lens","bool":false},{"option":"Ciliary process","bool":true}]},{"id":47,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The most common cause of blindness in diabetes is due to which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Corneal opacity","bool":false},{"option":"Conjunctivitis","bool":false},{"option":"Retinopathy","bool":true},{"option":"Lens dislocation","bool":false},{"option":"Glaucoma","bool":false}]},{"id":48,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Union of what structures form the medial orbital margin?","answers":[{"option":"Lacrimal and zygomatic bone","bool":false},{"option":"Frontal and zygomatic bone","bool":false},{"option":"Frontal and maxillary bone","bool":false},{"option":"Lacrimal and maxillary bone","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":49,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The body (anterior two-thirds) of the tongue is developed from what structure?","answers":[{"option":"Hypobranchial eminence","bool":false},{"option":"Tuberculum impar","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral lingual swellings","bool":true},{"option":"Copula","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":50,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Visual impairment in diabetes is due to all of the following except:","answers":[{"option":"Damage to the rods","bool":true},{"option":"Occlusion of retinal arteries","bool":false},{"option":"Cataract at an early age","bool":false},{"option":"Retinal detachment","bool":false},{"option":"Neovascularization","bool":false}]},{"id":51,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The site of union between the primary and secondary palate is identified as what in the adult?","answers":[{"option":"Uvula","bool":false},{"option":"Median palatal raphe","bool":false},{"option":"Passavant's ridge","bool":false},{"option":"Foramen cecum","bool":false},{"option":"Incisive foramen","bool":true}]},{"id":52,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is involved in rotational acceleration?","answers":[{"option":"Macula","bool":false},{"option":"Cristae ampularis","bool":true},{"option":"Saccule","bool":false},{"option":"Organ of corti","bool":false},{"option":"Utricle","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"The middle ear cavity develops from what structure?","answers":[{"option":"First pharyngeal pouch","bool":true},{"option":"First pharyngeal arch","bool":false},{"option":"Auditory vesicle","bool":false},{"option":"Second pharyngeal arch","bool":false},{"option":"First pharyngeal cleft","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Ligation of what artery will relieve chronic nose bleeds?","answers":[{"option":"Sphenopalatine artery","bool":true},{"option":"Posterior ethmoidal artery","bool":false},{"option":"Anterior ethmoidal artery","bool":false},{"option":"Facial artery","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":55,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is involved in hearing?","answers":[{"option":"Saccule","bool":false},{"option":"Semicircular canal","bool":false},{"option":"Cochlea","bool":true},{"option":"Utricle","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false}]},{"id":56,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Taste fibres from circumvallate papillae pass through what nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Lingual nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Chorda tympani","bool":false}]},{"id":57,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"What is true about the chorda tympani nerve?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Supplies the parotid gland","bool":false},{"option":"Contain postganglionic parasympathetic fibres","bool":false},{"option":"Joins lingual nerve in the infratemporal fossa","bool":true},{"option":"Is a branch of glossopharnygeal nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":58,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Dry eyes result from a lesion at which one of the following ganglions?","answers":[{"option":"Superior cervical","bool":false},{"option":"Pterygopalatine","bool":true},{"option":"Otic","bool":false},{"option":"Ciliary","bool":false},{"option":"Sphenopalatine","bool":false}]},{"id":59,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"All of the following muscles are supplied by the hypoglossal nerve except which?","answers":[{"option":"Thyrohyoid","bool":false},{"option":"Palatoglossus","bool":true},{"option":"Genioglossus","bool":false},{"option":"Geniohyoid","bool":false},{"option":"All of these are supplied by hypoglossal","bool":false}]},{"id":60,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is correct regarding the cochlea?","answers":[{"option":"Has helicotrema at base","bool":false},{"option":"Tectorial membrane forms basal lamina of hair cells","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Reissner's membrane lies towards the scala vestibuli","bool":true},{"option":"Contains maculae","bool":false}]},{"id":61,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Axons of which cells form the optic nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Ganglion cells","bool":true},{"option":"Rod cells","bool":false},{"option":"Bipolar cells","bool":false},{"option":"Amacrine cells","bool":false},{"option":"Horizontal cells","bool":false}]},{"id":62,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following statements is incorrect, if any, about neuroepithelium?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"These are specialized cells for the reception of taste","bool":false},{"option":"It forms nasal mucosa","bool":false},{"option":"It is simple cuboidal epithelium","bool":true},{"option":"It is present in cochlea","bool":false}]},{"id":63,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following types of papillae does not contain tastebuds?","answers":[{"option":"Filliform","bool":true},{"option":"Circumvallate","bool":false},{"option":"Fungiform","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Foliate","bool":false}]},{"id":64,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Which of the following is true about the venous drainage of the face?","answers":[{"option":"The pterygoid venous plexus does not drain to the maxillary vein","bool":false},{"option":"Deep facial veins drains into the pterygoid plexus","bool":true},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"The sphenopalatine, deep temporal, masseteric, and buccal veins are not the tributaries of the pterygoid venous plexus","bool":false},{"option":"The pterygoid plexus does not drain the nasal cavity and paranasal sinuses","bool":false}]},{"id":65,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2018","question":"Dorsum of the tongue is lined by which epithelium?","answers":[{"option":"Pseudostratified columnar","bool":false},{"option":"Stratified squamous partially keratinized","bool":true},{"option":"Stratified squamous non-keratinized","bool":false},{"option":"Stratified squamous keratinized","bool":false},{"option":"Stratified columnar","bool":false}]}]
export default arr